{
  "flashcard": [
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "what is 1+4",
      "answer": "8",
      "date": "4/1/2024 at 6:40",
      "status": "Learned"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which class is superior to Cosmic?",
      "answer": "Mystic",
      "date": "4/1/2024 at 5:30",
      "status": "Noted"
    },
    {
      "status": null,
      "id": 4,
      "question": "What is square root of 81?",
      "answer": "9",
      "date": "3/1/2024 at 21:40"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "2023 GOTY?",
      "answer": "Baldur's Gate 3",
      "date": "4/1/2024 at 5:10",
      "status": "Noted"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "2022 GOTY?",
      "answer": "Elden Ring",
      "date": "4/1/2024 at 5:10",
      "status": "Noted"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "2020 GOTY?",
      "answer": "Ghost Of Tsushima",
      "date": "4/1/2024 at 5:10",
      "status": "Noted"
    },
    {
      "status": null,
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Сколько весит килограмм арбуза?",
      "answer": "1000",
      "date": "3/1/2024 at 21:40"
    },
    {
      "status": null,
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Are you the strongest because you're Satoru Gojo?",
      "answer": "Or are you Satoru Gojo because you're the strongest?",
      "date": "3/1/2024 at 21:40"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "What color is orange?",
      "answer": "Orange",
      "date": "4/1/2024 at 5:27",
      "status": "Want to Learn"
    },
    {
      "status": null,
      "id": 13,
      "question": "How much is 10+50?",
      "answer": "60",
      "date": "3/1/2024 at 21:40"
    },
    {
      "status": null,
      "id": 14,
      "question": "How old Are the Great Wall of China?",
      "answer": "3000 years old",
      "date": "3/1/2024 at 21:40"
    },
    {
      "status": null,
      "id": 15,
      "question": "hello",
      "answer": "bye",
      "date": "3/1/2024 at 21:40"
    },
    {
      "status": null,
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Do you like this website?",
      "answer": "YES",
      "date": "3/1/2024 at 21:40"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "Is this real chat??",
      "answer": "no",
      "date": "4/1/2024 at 6:0",
      "status": "Noted"
    },
    {
      "status": null,
      "id": 20,
      "question": "почему",
      "answer": "потому",
      "date": "3/1/2024 at 21:41"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "2+2*2",
      "answer": "6",
      "date": "4/1/2024 at 7:45",
      "status": "Want to Learn"
    },
    {
      "question": "Adam Warlock is...",
      "answer": "a Cosmic ",
      "date": "4/1/2024 at 7:44",
      "id": 22
    }
  ]
}